eforum.com 2018-05-10

# Privacy | Internet Marketing Forum

## Information Collection and Use

We respect each site visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website. For each visitor to our website, our web-server automatically recognizes NO information regarding the domain or e-mail address. The information we collect is: 

  * used to improve the content of our Web page
  * used to notify visitors about updates to our Web site
  * never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes
  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
  * This site collects cookies ([Definition of Cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie))
  * Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Registration is not required to enter our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors of this feature. eForum.com is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that kids' information is protected. 

## eForum Anti-Spam Policy

eForum strictly enforces a no tolerance policy when it comes to spam. We prohibit the sending of unsolicited mass messages of any kind. 

## Disclosure

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to eForum or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. 

  * We sometimes receive compensation from some of the companies whose products we review and recommend on site.

## eForum Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy for eForum, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

Type your status and hit the enter key!

 **My Status**  

 **I am...**  
AvailableInvisibleBusyOffline  

Disable sound notifications

Disable popup notifications

Chat Now (0)
